Finding Aid for the Collection of Television Film Scripts PASC.0074
UCLA Library Special Collections
- MIDNIGHT OFFERINGS, (11/12/1980) (Box >141)
- MILES TO GO BEFORE I SLEEP, (10/10/1974) (Box >150)
  Writers: Parker, Judith; Svanoe, Bill
- MIND OF A KILLER, (1/17/1992) (Box >207)
  Writers: Epstein, Jacob; Solarz, Ken
- MIRACLE ON 34TH STREET, (7/9/1973) (Box >130)
  Writers: Rosebrook, Jeb
- MIRACLE ON ICE, (10/31/1980) (Box > 52)
  Writers: Chetwynd, L.
- MIRACLE WORKER (THE), (no date) (Box > 52)
  Writers: Gibson, W.
- MIRROR, MIRROR, (3/1/1979) (Box > 94)
  Writers: Appet, Leah; Dennis, Charles
- MIRROR, MIRROR, (no date) (Box > 21)
- MIRRORS, (8/22/1984) (Box >191)
  Writers: Lipton, James
- MISS ALL-AMERICAN BEAUTY, (3/5/1982) (Box > 60)
  Writers: Audley, Nancy; Tracy, Emily
- MISS EVERS BOYS, (2/22/1997) (Box >240)
- MISS HAWAIIN TROPIC INTERNATIONAL PAGEANT (1986 Special), (no date) (Box >231)
- MISSING PIECES, (2/14/1982) (Box >148)
  Writers: Hodges, Mike; Alexander, Karl
- MISSION OF THE SHARK, (1/1/1991) (Box >208)
- MISTRAL'S DAUGHTER, (12/1/1983) (Box > 53)
  Writers: Sisson, R. A.
- MISTRAL'S DAUGHTER (PART I), (2/15/1984) (Box >187)
  Writers: Freely, Terence
- MISTRAL'S DAUGHTER (PART II), (2/1/1984) (Box >188)
  Writers: Sisson, Rosemary Anne; Feely, Terence
- MISTRAL'S DAUGHTER (PART III), (2/24/1984) (Box >187)
  Writers: Sisson, Rosemary Anne
- MISTRESS, (3/3/1987) (Box > 82)
- MISTRESS OF PARADISE (FORMERLY: DARK SECRET OF BLACK BAYOU), (5/26/1981) (Box >103)
  Writers: Foster, Bennett
- MODESTY BLAISE, (2/12/1982) (Box >209)
- MOLONEY, (9/7/1995) (Box >212)
  Writers: Bass, Ronald; Rusconi, Jane
- MOM (THE) WOLFMAN AND ME, (12/21/1979) (Box > 99)
  Writers: Levy, Edmond
- MONEY ON THE SIDE, (5/21/1982) (Box > 7)
- MONEY TO BURN, (7/11/1973) (Box >246)
  Writers: Schwartz, Elroy
- MONK (THE), (no date) (Box >253)
  Writers: Barrett, Tony; Edwards, Blake
- MONK (THE), (no date) (Box >253)
  Writers: Barrett, Tony; Spelling, Aaron
- MONK (THE), (no date) (Box >253)
- MONK (THE), (2/13/1969) (Box >253)
  Writers: Edwards, Blake
- MONK (THE), (no date) (Box >253)
- MONK (THE) (A DIFFERENT KIND OF DYING), (no date) (Box >253)
  Writers: Lasko, Edward J.
- MONK (THE) (GOING AWAY PRESENT), (10/9/1969) (Box >253)
  Writers: Radnitz, Brad
- MONK (THE) (ONE FOR THE MONEY), (no date) (Box >253)
  Writers: Field, Gustave
- MONTANA, (3/6/1988) (Box > 82)
  Writers: McMurtry, Larry
- MOON OF THE WOLF, (5/3/1972) (Box >129)
  Writers: Sapinsley, Alvin
- MOONLIGHT, (2/14/1980) (Box > 7)
- MOONLIGHT, (10/25/1979) (Box > 7)
- MORNING AFTER (THE), (10/1/1973) (Box >131)
  Writers: Matheson, Richard
- MOTHER AND DAUGHTER: THE LOVING WAR, (5/30/1979) (Box >100)
- MOTHER AND DAUGHTER: THE LOVING WAR, (10/12/1979) (Box >144)
- MOTHER SETON, (11/13/1979) (Box > 53)
  Writers: Denker, H.
- MOTHERS AND DAUGHTERS, (no date) (Box > 7)
- MOTOWN 25: YESTERDAY, TODAY, FOREVER (Special), (no date) (Box >230)
- MOVIOLA: THE SCARLETT O'HARA WAR, (no date) (Box > 72)
  Writers: Hanley, William; Kanin, Garson
- MOVIOLA: THE SILENT LOVERS, (12/20/1980) (Box > 53)
- MOVIOLA: THIS YEAR'S BLONDE, (no date) (Box > 72)
  Writers: Lee, James; Kanin, Garson
- MR. AND MRS. LOVING, (no date) (Box >254)
  Writers: Friedenberg, Richard
- MR. HORN (PART II), (5/1/1978) (Box > 83)
  Writers: Goldman, William
- MR. HORN (PARTS I & II), (5/26/1978) (Box >115)
- MR. LITTLE (SPECIAL), (2/25/1981) (Box >244)
  Writers: Olson, Glen; Baker, Rod
- MRS. DELAFIELD WANTS TO MARRY, (8/21/1985) (Box > 60)
  Writers: Prideaux, James
- MRS. SUNDANCE, (9/13/1973) (Box >130)
  Writers: Knofp, Christopher
- MURDER 101, (11/5/1990) (Box >126)
  Writers: Johansen, Roy; Condon, Bill
- MURDER AT MY DOOR, (1/16/1993) (Box >205)
  Writers: Sullivan, Patti
- MURDER CAN HURT YOU!, (2/7/1980) (Box > 97)
  Writers: Friedman, Ron
- MURDER IN COWETA COUNTY, (no date) (Box > 82)
- MURDER IN COWETA COUNTY, (8/20/1982) (Box > 82)
- MURDER IN COWETA COUNTY, (5/5/1982) (Box > 82)
- MURDER IN MALIBU, (no date) (Box >249)
- MURDER IN MISSISSIPPI, (4/10/1989) (Box > 34)
  Writers: Weiser, Stanley
- MURDER IN PARADISE, (11/17/1988) (Box > 75)
  Writers: DiPego, Gerald; McCutchen, Bill
- MURDER IN PEYTON PLACE, (5/24/1977) (Box >120)
- MURDER IN SPACE 1996, (no date) (Box > 84)
- MURDER IN TEXAS (PART I), (10/7/1980) (Box > 18)
- MURDER IN TEXAS (PART II), (10/10/1980) (Box > 18)
- MURDER LIVE, (6/28/1996) (Box >248)
  Writers: Bertolet, Chris
- MURDER OF MARY PHAGAN (THE), (12/12/1986) (Box >144)
  Writers: Lane, Jeffrey; Stevens, George Jr.
- MURDER ON FLIGHT 502, (8/21/1975) (Box >170)
- MURDER WITH MIRRORS, (8/27/1984) (Box >201)
  Writers: Eckstein, George
- MURDER WITHOUT MOTIVE: THE EDMUND PERRY STORY, (5/9/1990) (Box >128)
- MURDEROUS VISION, (8/26/1990) (Box >214)
  Writers: Gulino, Paul
- MUSIC OF YOUR LIFE (Special), (no date) (Box >232)
- MY DEAR UNCLE SHERLOCK (SPECIAL), (1/7/1977) (Box >243)
  Writers: Starr, Manya
- MY FATHER'S HOUSE, (no date) (Box >212)
  Writers: Sontag, David
- MY MOTHER'S SECRET LIFE, (no date) (Box > 22)
- MY NAME IS BILL W., (11/28/1988) (Box >160)
  Writers: Borchert, William G.
- MY NAME IS KATE, (12/11/1992) (Box >242)
- MY WICKED, WICKED WAYS, (5/23/1983) (Box >192)
  Writers: Keating, Doris; Trump, Jill
- MY WICKED, WICKED WAYS, (9/30/1983) (Box > 53)
  Writers: Keating, D.
- MY WICKED, WICKED WAYS "THE LEGEND OF ERROL FLYNN", (9/30/1983) (Box >193)
- MYSTERIOUS TWO, (3/23/1979) (Box > 24)
  Writers: Sherman, Gary; Guss, Jack
- MYSTERY DANCE, (12/16/1993) (Box >248)
  Writers: Goldman, Wendy; Wells, John
- N.Y.P.D. MOUNTED, (3/20/1990) (Box >128)
  Writers: Hasburgh, Patrick; Ruggiero Jr., Alfonse
- NAKED LIE, (no date) (Box > 15)
- NASHVILLE GRAB (THE), (no date) (Box > 22)
- NBC ALL-STAR HAPPY HOUR (1983 Special), (no date) (Box >236)
- NBC ALL-STAR HOUR (1984 Special), (no date) (Box >236)
- NBC DANCE PILOT (JUMP!), (no date) (Box >228)
- NEVADA SMITH, (12/17/1974) (Box >179)
  Writers: Hayes, John Michael; Rackin, Martin
- NEVADA SMITH, (11/25/1974) (Box >161)
- NEW ADVENTURES OF HEIDI (THE), (5/25/1978) (Box >152)
- NEWS AT ELEVEN, (7/1/1985) (Box > 1)
- NICK KNIGHT, (1/9/1989) (Box > 65)
  Writers: Parriott, James D.
- NICKY'S WORLD, (12/17/1973) (Box >169)
  Writers: Katz, William; Adler, Edward
- NIGHT CRIES, (11/7/1977) (Box >118)
  Writers: Taggert, Brian; Lawrence, Tony
- NIGHT OWL, (8/7/1992) (Box >212)
  Writers: Powell, Ann; Schacht, Rose
- NIGHT PARTNERS, (1/26/1983) (Box >159)
  Writers: Merl, Judy; Myers, Paul Eric
- NIGHT THE BRIDGE FELL DOWN (THE), (no date) (Box > 53)
  Writers: David, M.R.; Allen, Irwin
- NIGHT THE CITY SCREAMED (THE), (12/3/1979) (Box > 93)
- NIGHT THE CITY SCREAMED (THE), (5/13/1980) (Box >141)
  Writers: Brody, Larry; Meadow, Herb
- NIGHT THE CITY SCREAMED (THE), (6/6/1980) (Box > 91)
  Writers: Brody, Larry
- NIGHTMARE, (no date) (Box >109)
  Writers: Wiltse, David
- NIGHTMARE IN BADHAM COUNTY, (7/28/1976) (Box >155)
  Writers: Heims, Jo
- NO PLACE TO RUN, (4/20/1972) (Box >118)
- NORMA AND MARILYN, (5/8/1995) (Box >214)
  Writers: Isaacs, Jill
- NORMAN ROCKWELL'S AMERICA, (10/23/1969) (Box >251)
  Writers: Baker, Herbert; Silverman, Treva
- NORTH AND SOUTH (PARTS I, II, III, IV), (10/3/1984) (Box > 54)
  Writers: Edwards, P.
- NORTH BEACH & RAWHIDE, (2/4/1985) (Box > 8)
  Writers: Sangster, Jimmy
- NORTH BEACH & RAWHIDE, (10/8/1984) (Box > 84)
- NORTH'S WAR, (no date) (Box >248)
  Writers: Wimmer, Kurt
- NOT IN FRONT OF THE CHILDREN, (2/17/1981) (Box > 73)
- NOT IN MY FAMILY, (1/20/1992) (Box >181)
  Writers: Cacaci, Joe
- NOT JUST ANOTHER AFFAIR, (3/16/1982) (Box >149)
  Writers: Mishkin, Philip; Podell, Rick
- NOT MY KID, (6/28/1984) (Box >196)
  Writers: Knopf, Christopher
- NOT OF THIS WORLD, (7/24/1990) (Box >126)
  Writers: Glass, Robert
- NOT OUR SON, (9/28/1994) (Box >204)
- OBSESSED WITH A MARRIED WOMAN, (no date) (Box > 22)
- OBSESSION, (10/18/1991) (Box >211)
  Writers: Peckinpah, David
- OBSESSIVE LOVE, (2/4/1984) (Box >169)
  Writers: Popescu, Petru; Friedman, Iris
- OF THEE I SING (SPECIAL), (5/17/1972) (Box >249)
  Writers: Kaufman, George S.; Ryskind, Morrie
- OHMS, (5/5/1979) (Box >197)
  Writers: Case, Gene
- OHMS, (3/19/1979) (Box >110)
- OKLAHOMA CITY DOLLS (THE), (3/10/1980) (Box > 79)
- OLD MAN, (no date) (Box >240)
  Writers: Foote, Horton
- OLD MAN WHO CRIED WOLF! (THE), (4/6/1970) (Box >110)
  Writers: Davis, Luther
- ON WINGS OF EAGLES (PART I), (no date) (Box > 91)
  Writers: Rolfe, Sam H.; Follett, Ken
- ONCE UPON A SPY, (10/28/1979) (Box > 54)
  Writers: Sangster, J.
- ONCE YOU MEET A STRANGER, (3/7/1996) (Box >214)
  Writers: Wallace, Tommy Lee
- ONE COOKS (THE) OTHER DOESN'T, (1/5/1983) (Box >162)
  Writers: Grusin, Larry; Ross, Mike Lloyd
- ONE IN A MILLION: THE RON LEFLORE STORY, (4/28/1978) (Box >181)
- ONE OF MY WIVES IS MISSING, (9/12/1975) (Box >171)
  Writers: Stone, Peter
- ONLY WITH MARRIED MEN, (10/7/1974) (Box >121)
  Writers: Davis, Jerry
- OPEN ADMISSIONS, (no date) (Box > 77)
  Writers: Lauro, Shirley
- OPERATION (THE), (4/23/1989) (Box >241)
  Writers: Gorghi, Douglas Stefan
- ORDEAL OF PATTY HEARST (THE), (4/17/1978) (Box >131)
- ORDEAL OF PATTY HEARST (THE), (10/19/1978) (Box >164)
- ORPHAN TRAIN, (4/23/1979) (Box > 96)
  Writers: Lampell, Millard; Craviotto, Darlene
- OTHER LOVER (THE), (9/28/1984) (Box > 92)
  Writers: Title, Susan; Parker, Judith
- OTHER VICTIM (THE), (5/21/1981) (Box > 94)
- OTHER WOMAN (THE), (no date) (Box >185)
  Writers: Garrett, Lila; Meara, Anne
- OUT OF THE PAST (Released as Out of Annie's Past), (7/25/1994) (Box >254)
  Writers: Fenjves, Pablo
- OUT ON THE EDGE, (2/9/1989) (Box >185)
  Writers: Balcer, Rene; Martinez, Al
- OUTLAWS, (no date) (Box > 25)
- OUTRAGE!, (no date) (Box > 22)
- OUTSIDE WOMAN (THE), (8/29/1987) (Box > 14)
- OVERKILL: THE AILEEN WUORNOS STORY, (4/22/1992) (Box >183)
  Writers: Mills, Fred
- PACKIN' IT IN, (8/3/1982) (Box >195)
  Writers: Jones, Patricia; Reiker, Donald
- PALYING WITH FIRE, (7/10/1984) (Box >197)
- PANCHO BARNES, (5/5/1988) (Box > 75)
  Writers: Hayes, John Michael; Andre', Blue
- PANIC ON THE 5:22, (8/13/1974) (Box >105)
  Writers: Price, Eugene
- PARADE, (no date) (Box > 10)
- PARENT TRAP III, (1/10/1989) (Box >138)
  Writers: Donner, Jill
- PART OF THE FAMILY, A, (no date) (Box >212)
  Writers: Madden, David
- PASSIONS, (12/5/1983) (Box >169)
  Writers: Greek, Janet; Maxwell, Robin
- PAST MIDNIGHT, (9/27/1990) (Box >126)
  Writers: Norwood, Frank
- PAST MIDNIGHT, (1/17/1990) (Box >129)
- PATRICIA NEAL STORY (THE), (10/16/1980) (Box >163)
  Writers: Anderson, Robert
- PAYOFF, (8/7/1990) (Box > 89)
  Writers: Weisberg, David; Cook, Douglas S.
- PENALTY PHASE (THE), (no date) (Box >145)
  Writers: Hickman, Gale Patrick
- PENALTY PHASE (THE), (5/26/1986) (Box >168)
- PEOPLE LIKE US (PARTS I, II), (9/15/1989) (Box > 68)
  Writers: Crowley, Mart; Shelley, Kathleen A.
- PERFECT GENTLEMEN, (9/9/1977) (Box >154)
  Writers: Ephron, Nora
- PERFECT MATCH, A, (2/5/1980) (Box > 93)
- PETER GUNN, (10/3/1988) (Box > 76)
- PETER THE GREAT, (3/5/1984) (Box > 55)
  Writers: Schiller, L.
- PEYTON PLACE: NEXT GENERATION, (11/6/1984) (Box > 55)
  Writers: Lakin, R.
- PEYTON PLACE: NEXT GENERATION, (1/17/1985) (Box > 55)
- PHILLY HEAT, (11/30/1992) (Box >206)
  Writers: Fontana, Tom
- PHOENIX (THE), (3/13/1980) (Box >112)
  Writers: Lawrence, Anthony; Lawrence, Nancy
- PIANO FOR MRS. CIMINO, A, (8/31/1981) (Box >164)
- PIANO FOR MRS. CIMINO, A, (no date) (Box >124)
- PIANO LESSON (THE), (8/10/1994) (Box >219)
  Writers: Wilson, August
- PIGS VS. FREAKS, (7/28/1980) (Box > 55)
  Writers: Dawson, G.
- PINK LIGHTNING, (10/26/1990) (Box >208)
  Writers: Monpere, Carol
- PLACE TO CALL HOME, A, (12/12/1985) (Box > 34)
  Writers: Sobieski, Carol; Taylor, Jeri
- PLAYBOY BUNNY OF THE YEAR PAGEANT, (3/18/1974) (Box >188)
- PLAYER (THE), (1/9/1997) (Box >254)
  Writers: Kramer, Richard; Tolkin, Michael
- PLAYING FOR TIME, (no date) (Box > 22)
- PLAYING FOR TIME, (11/6/1979) (Box > 22)
  Writers: Miller, Arthur
- PLAYMATES, (5/15/1972) (Box >119)
- PLEASURE COVE, (7/7/1978) (Box > 56)
  Writers: Shaw, L.
- PLEASURE PALACE, (7/12/1979) (Box >144)
- PLEASURE PALACE, (1/28/1980) (Box >137)
- PLEASURE PALACE, (11/19/1979) (Box >137)
- PLEASURE PALACE, (2/22/1980) (Box >137)
- PLOT TO MURDER HITLER (THE) (SPECIAL), (8/8/1971) (Box >251)
  Writers: Guenette, Robert
- POISONED BY LOVE: THE KERN COUNTY MURDERS, (7/18/1992) (Box >184)
  Writers: Brattlestreet, Caliope; Glantz, Stephen
- POLICE STORY: THE FREEWAY KILLINGS, (9/17/1986) (Box > 82)
- PORTRAIT OF A SHOWGIRL (FORMERLY: LAS VEGAS), (7/30/1981) (Box >103)
  Writers: Merrill, Bob
- PORTRAIT OF AN ESCORT (FORMERLY: PROFESSIONAL DATE), (1/2/1980) (Box >103)
- POWER, AN AMERICAN SAGA, (12/27/1978) (Box > 9)
- PRAY TV, (6/17/1981) (Box >121)
- PREPPY MURDER (THE), (6/3/1989) (Box > 75)
  Writers: Herzfeld, John
- PRESCRIPTION: MURDER, (5/17/1967) (Box >124)
- PRETENDERS (THE), (8/22/1985) (Box > 73)
  Writers: Poole, Duane; Swale, Tom
- PREY FOR US ALL see LOVE, CHEAT AND STEAL, (no date) (Box >)
- PRIDE AND PREJUDICE, (no date) (Box >228)
  Writers: Ausntin, Jane; Davies, Andrew
- PRIDE OF JESSE HALLAM (THE), (8/15/1980) (Box >113)
  Writers: Clauser, Suzanne
- PRIME SUSPECT, (4/5/1981) (Box >107)
  Writers: Graham, Douglas
- PRINCESS DAISY, (4/1/1983) (Box >189)
  Writers: Hammond, Diana
- PRIVATE SESSIONS, (10/17/1984) (Box >105)
  Writers: Thomas, Thom; Seltzer, David
- PRIZE PULITZER (THE), (1/21/1989) (Box > 34)
  Writers: Sackett, Nancy
- PROBABLE CAUSE, (3/2/1993) (Box >205)
  Writers: Salwen, Harold; Ziller, Paul
- PROMISE KEPT, A: THE OKSANA BAIUL STORY, (8/18/1994) (Box >216)
  Writers: Shapiro, Mimi Rothman; Wells, Bill
- PROMISED LAND (THE) LEGEND OF THE BLACK INDIANS, (2/28/1994) (Box >247)
  Writers: Hendrie, Alexander
- PROPHET OF EVIL, (2/1/1993) (Box >208)
- PROTOTYPE, (4/20/1983) (Box >153)
- PUNCH AND JODY, (2/27/1974) (Box >122)
- PURSUIT (PART I, II), (5/5/1988) (Box > 67)
  Writers: Waldron, Gy; Bast, William; Huson, Paul
- QB VII, (no date) (Box >131)
  Writers: Anhalt, Edward
- QUARTERBACK PRINCESS, (3/18/1983) (Box >132)
- QUARTERBACK PRINCESS, (7/21/1983) (Box >149)
- QUEEN, (1/17/1992) (Box >123)
  Writers: Stevens, David; Haley, Alex
- QUEEN OF THE STARDUST BALLROOM, (4/2/1974) (Box >195)
- QUEEN, PART I, (9/2/1991) (Box >182)
- QUEEN, PART II, (4/19/1991) (Box >182)
- QUEST (THE), (no date) (Box > 22)
- QUEST (THE), (12/1/1975) (Box > 56)
  Writers: Wynn, T.K.
- QUESTION OF GUILT, A, (8/31/1977) (Box >118)
  Writers: Willis, Jack; Willis, Mary
- QUESTION OF LOVE, A, (10/12/1977) (Box >186)
- QUESTOR TAPES (THE), (11/29/1972) (Box >242)
  Writers: Coon, Gene
- QUICKSILVER HIGHWAY, (11/5/1996) (Box >219)
  Writers: Garris, Mick
- R & B COUNTDOWN (Special), (no date) (Box >225)
- RADIANT CITY, (9/7/1988) (Box >211)
- RAGE, (no date) (Box > 56)
  Writers: Rubino, G.
- RAGE, (4/28/1980) (Box > 56)
- RAGE OF ANGELS, (7/7/1982) (Box >151)
  Writers: Joseph, Robert L.
- RAGE OF ANGELS, (4/2/1982) (Box >131)
- RAINBOW, (no date) (Box >154)
  Writers: McGreevey, John; Finch, Christopher
- RAINBOW DRIVE, (2/9/1990) (Box >207)
  Writers: Phillips, Bill; Cohen, Bennett
- RAPE OF DR. WILLIS, (8/5/1991) (Box >213)
  Writers: Gethers, Steve; Goldstone, Deena
- RATINGS GAME (THE), (4/26/1984) (Box > 73)
  Writers: Mulholland, Jim; Barrie, Michael
- REAR VIEW MIRROR, (no date) (Box > 9)
- REASON TO LIVE (FORMERLY: MY LIFE, YOUR LIFE), (4/16/1984) (Box >102)
  Writers: Lewin, Robert
- REASON TO LIVE, A, (4/28/1984) (Box >180)
- RED ALERT, (2/10/1977) (Box >156)
  Writers: Stern, Sandor; King, Harold
- RED EARTH, WHITE EARTH, (no date) (Box > 13)
- RED FLAG: THE ULTIMATE GAME, (3/13/1981) (Box > 30)
  Writers: Cook, T.S.
- RED WIND, (9/14/1988) (Box >145)
  Writers: Noonan, Tom
- RELUCTANT ASTRONAUT (THE), (3/31/1966) (Box >255)
  Writers: Fritzell, Jim; Greenbaum, Everett
- RELUCTANT HEROES (THE), (3/17/1970) (Box >106)
  Writers: Hoffman, Herman
- REMEMBER WHEN, (10/16/1974) (Box >105)
  Writers: Raucher, Herman
- RENDEZVOUS HOTEL, (3/21/1978) (Box >180)
  Writers: Kalish, Austin; Kalish, Irma
- RESCUE FROM GILLIGAN'S ISLAND, (6/21/1978) (Box >154)
  Writers: Schwartz, Sherwood; Schwartz, Elroy
- RETURN OF DR. MARCUS WELBY M.D. (THE), (11/2/1983) (Box > 93)
- RETURN OF MOD SQUAD (THE), (4/4/1979) (Box >103)
  Writers: Janes, Robert
- RETURN TO GREEN ACRES, (12/1/1989) (Box > 85)
  Writers: Heller, Craig; Shulman, Guy
- RETURN TO MAYBERRY, (1/24/1986) (Box >175)
  Writers: Bullock, Harvey; Greenbaum, Everett
- RETURN TO MAYBERRY, (1/15/1986) (Box >191)
- REUNION (THE), (no date) (Box > 23)
- REVENGE, (7/13/1971) (Box >106)
- REVENGE OF AL CAPONE (THE), (no date) (Box > 15)
- REVENGE OF AL CAPONE (THE), (9/15/1988) (Box >185)
- REVENGE OF THE STEPFORD WIVES, (7/2/1980) (Box > 94)
- REWARD, (2/11/1980) (Box > 18)
  Writers: Miller, Jason
- RHINEMANN EXCHANGE (THE) (PART 1,2,3,4), (1/28/1977) (Box >200)
  Writers: Collins, Richard
- RHYTHM AND BLUES, (12/13/1991) (Box >211)
  Writers: Moffet, Jordan
- RICH MAN, POOR MAN (8-PART SHOW), (5/2/1975) (Box > 76)
  Writers: Riesner, D.
- RICH MEN, SINGLE WOMEN, (9/15/1989) (Box > 75)
  Writers: Brown, James Harmon; Esensten, Barbara
- RICHEST CAT IN THE WORLD (THE), (12/1/1985) (Box >192)
  Writers: Olsen, Alfa-Betty; Efron, Marshall
- RICHEST CAT IN THE WORLD (THE), (11/24/1985) (Box >138)
- RICHEST CAT IN THE WORLD (THE), (10/22/1985) (Box >160)
  Writers: Rose, Andy; Gorby, Alex
- RIGHT OF THE PEOPLE (THE), (7/23/1985) (Box >136)
- RIGHT OF WAY, (8/16/1982) (Box >181)
  Writers: Lees, Richard
- RIGHT OF WAY, (8/1/1982) (Box > 25)
- RIGHT TO KILL?, (2/26/1985) (Box > 71)
- RINGO (SPECIAL), (1/29/1978) (Box >246)
- RIO SHANNON, (3/4/1992) (Box >186)
  Writers: Bergman, Linda
- RITA HAYWORTH (THE) LOVE GODDESS, (2/20/1983) (Box >194)
  Writers: Kean, Arthur E.
- RIVKIN: BOUNTY HUNTER, (4/23/1980) (Box > 72)
- ROAD RAIDERS, (2/4/1988) (Box >104)
  Writers: Larson, Glen A.; Jones, Mark
- ROAD RAIDERS, (3/6/1988) (Box >104)
- ROAD RAIDERS, (no date) (Box > 17)
- ROBERT KENNEDY AND HIS TIMES, (9/21/1983) (Box > 58)
  Writers: Green, W.
- ROBERT KENNEDY AND HIS TIMES (PARTS I, II, III), (10/20/1980) (Box > 57)
  Writers: Greenberg, S.R.
- ROBIN HOOD, (10/18/1990) (Box >257)
- ROBIN WILLIAMS 1982 SPECIAL (Special), (no date) (Box >229)
- ROCKABYE, (8/16/1985) (Box >197)
  Writers: Koenig, Laird
- ROCKABYE, (no date) (Box >206)
- ROCKABYE, (9/21/1981) (Box >250)
- RODEO GIRL, (3/5/1980) (Box >137)
  Writers: Powers, Katharyn Michaelian
- ROE VS. WADE, (4/4/1988) (Box > 30)
  Writers: CROSS, ALISON
- ROLL, FREDDY, ROLL, (9/4/1974) (Box >121)
  Writers: Persky, Bill; Denoff, Sam
- ROLLING MAN, (4/28/1971) (Box >119)
- ROLLING MAN, (12/3/1971) (Box >250)
  Writers: Karpf, Elinor; Karpf, Stephen
- ROMAN HOLIDAY, (4/14/1980) (Box > 33)
- ROOM UPSTAIRS (THE), (9/30/1986) (Box > 8)
  Writers: Lawson, Steve
- ROOSTER, (12/1/1981) (Box > 58)
  Writers: Larson, G.A.
- ROSEANNE AND TOM: A HOLLYWOOD MARRIAGE, (8/30/1994) (Box >247)
- ROSES ARE FOR THE RICH (PARTS I, II), (8/13/1986) (Box > 67)
- ROSIE: THE ROSEMARY CLOONEY STORY, (4/9/1982) (Box > 84)
  Writers: Coker, Katherine
- RUBY AND OSWALD, (no date) (Box >196)
  Writers: McGreevy, Michael; McGreevy, John
- RULES OF MARRIAGE (PART II), (10/30/1981) (Box > 58)
  Writers: Rose, R.
- RUMOR OF WAR, A (PART I), (11/13/1979) (Box > 1)
  Writers: Young, John Sacret
- RUMOR OF WAR, A (PART II), (11/13/1979) (Box > 1)
- RUNNING AGAINST TIME, (6/11/1990) (Box >127)
  Writers: Shapiro, Stanley; Glass, Bob
- RUNNING OUT, (9/24/1982) (Box >152)
  Writers: Guest, Elissa Haden
- RUNNING OUT, (11/1/1981) (Box > 9)
- RUNNING OUT, (10/4/1982) (Box > 60)
- S.O.S. TITANIC!, (12/8/1978) (Box > 99)
- S.O.S. TITANIC!, (12/20/1978) (Box > 83)
- SADAT, (3/7/1983) (Box >254)
- SADIE AND SON, (4/27/1987) (Box > 80)
- SALVAGE, (1/31/1978) (Box > 58)
  Writers: Ross, M.L.
- SAMARITAN: THE MITCH SNYDER STORY, (5/25/1974) (Box > 9)
- SAMSON AND DELILAH, (no date) (Box >254)
  Writers: Scott, Allan
- SAMSON AND DELILAH, (9/15/1983) (Box > 58)
- SAMSON AND DELILAH, (no date) (Box > 23)
- SAN BERDOO, (12/23/1988) (Box >206)
  Writers: Greisman, Gordon
- SANCTUARY OF FEAR, (10/25/1978) (Box >164)
- SANDAL SHEET, (no date) (Box > 25)
- SARAH, PLAIN AND TALL, (10/17/1989) (Box > 66)
  Writers: MacLachlan, Patricia
- SAVAGE BEES (THE), (no date) (Box >142)
- SAVAGE BEES (THE), (8/27/1976) (Box >166)
- SAVAGES, (5/20/1977) (Box >118)
- SAY GOODBYE, MAGGIE COLE, (4/10/1972) (Box >111)
  Writers: Stern, Sandor
- SCARED STRAIGHT! ANOTHER STORY, (12/26/1979) (Box >100)
- SCARLET AND THE BLACK (THE), (6/17/1982) (Box >122)
  Writers: Butler, David
- SCORNED AND SWINDLED, (1/19/1984) (Box > 73)
  Writers: Hoeffner, Karol Ann
- SCORNED AND SWINDLED, (11/28/1983) (Box >181)
- SCREEN ACTORS GUILD AWARDS (Special), (no date) (Box >226)
- SEALED WITH A KISS, (no date) (Box >255)
  Writers: Boyle, Bill
- SEALS, (7/11/1986) (Box > 34)
  Writers: Thomas, Jim; Thomas, John
- SEARCH FOR THE GODS, (3/29/1974) (Box >117)
  Writers: Miller, Herman; Pettus, Ken
- SEARCH FOR THE GODS, (9/30/1974) (Box >120)
- SECOND CHANCE, (no date) (Box >176)
  Writers: Morris, Michael
- SECOND NATURE, (11/3/1994) (Box >254)
  Writers: Frye, E. Max
- SECRET NIGHT CALLER, (no date) (Box >252)
  Writers: Presnell, Robert
- SECRET NIGHT CALLER (THE), (11/22/1974) (Box >150)
  Writers: Presnell, Robert Jr.
- SECRET OF LOST VALLEY (THE), (9/11/1978) (Box > 46)
- SECRET WEAPONS, (11/21/1984) (Box >138)
- SECRET WEAPONS, (no date) (Box > 23)
- SECRETS, (11/1/1976) (Box >163)
  Writers: Henerson, James; Crawford, Joanna
- SECRETS, (9/26/1975) (Box >108)
- SECRETS OF A MARRIED MAN, (10/11/1983) (Box > 10)
- SECRETS OF THREE HUNGRY WIVES, (2/17/1978) (Box >180)
- SEDUCED, (5/21/1984) (Box >175)
  Writers: Carner, Charles Robert
- SEE JANE RUN, (5/18/1994) (Box >242)
- SEEDING OF SARAH BURNS (THE), (11/7/1978) (Box >165)
- SEEDING OF SARAH BURNS (THE), (9/11/1978) (Box > 87)
  Writers: Stern, Sander
- SEIZURE, (4/18/1979) (Box >195)
- SENSITIVE, PASSIONATE MAN, A, (1/22/1977) (Box >120)
- SENTIMENTAL JOURNEY, (5/23/1983) (Box > 25)
- SEPTEMBER GUN, (4/4/1983) (Box >167)
  Writers: Norton, William
- SEPTEMBER GUN, (no date) (Box > 23)
- SERGEANT MATLOVICH VERSUS THE U.S. AIR FORCE, (1/10/1977) (Box >156)
- SESSIONS, (4/3/1983) (Box > 91)
  Writers: Turmer, Barbera
- SEX AND THE SINGLE PARENT, (5/23/1979) (Box > 24)
- SHADOW BOX (THE), (no date) (Box >153)
  Writers: Cristofer, Michael
- SHADOW IN THE STREETS, A, (12/4/1974) (Box >169)
  Writers: Black, John D.F.; Donner, Richard
- SHAME, (1/20/1992) (Box >123)
  Writers: Soladay, Rebecca
- SHANNON'S DEAL, (no date) (Box > 13)
- SHANNON'S DEAL, (no date) (Box > 31)
- SHATTERED SILENCE (THE), (9/7/1982) (Box > 59)
  Writers: Mann, A.
- SHATTERED SILENCE (THE), (10/6/1981) (Box > 59)
- SHATTERED VOWS, (3/27/1984) (Box >175)
  Writers: Levin, Audrey Davis; Wong, Mary Gilligan
- SHAUGHNESSY, (1/10/1996) (Box >220)
  Writers: Blinn, William; L'Amour, Louis
- SHE WAITS, (11/11/1971) (Box >136)
- SHE WAS MARKED FOR MURDER, (no date) (Box > 15)
- SHELL GAME, (no date) (Box >118)
  Writers: Bloom, Harold Jack
- SHE'S DRESSED TO KILL, (no date) (Box >152)
- SHE'S IN THE ARMY NOW, (12/12/1980) (Box >167)
- SHIRLEY MACLAINE SPECIAL (THE), (no date) (Box >237)
  Writers: Kohan, Buz
- SHIRTS/SKINS, (3/3/1973) (Box >120)
  Writers: Paltrow, Bruce
- SHOOTER, (12/10/1987) (Box > 75)
  Writers: Kline, Stephen; Kennerly, David Hume
- SHOOTING STARS, (2/3/1983) (Box > 10)
- SID CEASAR, IMOGENE...SPECIAL (THE) (SPECIAL), (no date) (Box >243)
- SIDE BY SIDE: THE TRUE STORY OF THE OSMOND FAMILY, (5/26/1981) (Box > 98)
  Writers: Wallengren, E.F.; Lazarus, Tom (story by)
- SIDE SHOW, (10/31/1978) (Box >116)
- SIDNEY SHORR, (11/12/1980) (Box >203)
  Writers: Baker, Marilyn Cantor
- SIEGE, (no date) (Box > 25)